<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="name_text">Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire!</string>
    <string name="avatar_image_description">Avatar Image</string>
    <string name="goblet_of_fire_description_text">Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire is a 2005 fantasy film directed by Mike Newell and distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures.[4] It is based on J. K. Rowling\'s 2000 novel of the same name. The film, which is the fourth instalment in the Harry Potter film series, was written by Steve Kloves and produced by David Heyman. The story follows Harry\'s fourth year at Hogwarts as he is chosen by the Goblet of Fire to compete in the Triwizard Tournament.  The film is the first of the series to receive a PG-13 certificate in the US, and a 12A in the UK, and stars Daniel Radcliffe as Harry Potter alongside Rupert Grint and Emma Watson as Harry\'s best friends Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger. It is the sequel to Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban and is followed by Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.  Filming began in early 2004. The Hogwarts scenes were shot at the Leavesden Film Studios. Five days after its release, the film had grossed over US$102 million at the North American box office, which is the third-highest first-weekend tally for a Harry Potter film behind Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows – Part 1 and Part 2. Goblet of Fire enjoyed an immensely successful run at the box office, earning $897 million worldwide, which made it the highest-grossing film of 2005 and the sixth-highest-grossing film in the Harry Potter series.  The film was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Art Direction, and won the BAFTA Award for Best Production Design. Goblet of Fire was the second film in the series to be released in IMAX. The film is one of the best-reviewed instalments within the series, being praised for the higher level of maturity and sophistication of its characters, plotline, tone, screenplay, and the performances of the lead actors.[5]</string>
    <string name="nickname_hint">Enter Your Nickname</string>
    <string name="done_button">Done</string>
</resources>
